improvepresentation.com 2016-03-15

# Website Privacy Policy | Improve Presentation

Last Modified: 12/06/2014 

## Introduction

Improve Presentation, Inc. a Delaware C-Corporation ("Company" or "We") respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy.

This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the website www.improvepresentation.com (our "Website") or when you purchase license, download, or use presentation templates or other digital goods published on the Website (the "Item") and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting and disclosing that information. 

This policy applies to information we collect:

  * On this Website.

  * In e-mail, text and other electronic messages between you and this Website. 

  * When you interact with our advertising and applications on third-party websites and services, if those applications or advertising include links to this policy. 

It does not apply to information collected by: 

  * us offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by Company or any third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries); or 

  * any third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries), including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from or on the Website 

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website or do not purchase license, download, or use the Item. By accessing, registering with or using this Website or the Item, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time. Your continued use of this Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates. 

## Children Under the Age of 13 

Our Website is not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any information to or on the Website. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on this Website or on or through any of its features/register on the Website, make any purchases through the Website, use any of the interactive or public comment features of this Website or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address or any screen name or user name you may use. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [contact@www.improvepresentation.com](mailto:contact@www.improvepresentation.com)

##  Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It 

We collect several types of information from and about users of our Website, including information: 

  * by which you may be personally identified, such as full name, e-mail address, telephone number, country, your company name, any other identifier by which you may be contacted online or offline (" **personal information** "); 

  * that is about you but individually does not identify you; and/or 

  * about your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Website and usage details. 
  * 

We collect this information: 

  * Directly from you when you provide it to us. 

  * Automatically as you navigate through the Website. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses and information collected through cookies, web beacons and other tracking technologie 

  * From third parties, for example from selz.com when you purchase license for the Item using selz.com service.

## Infromation You PRovide to Us.

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website. This includes information provided at the time of purchasing license for the Item, registering to use our Website, subscribing to our service, and other materials or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you enter a contest or promotion sponsored by us, and when you report a problem with our Website. 

  * Records and copies of your correspondence (including e-mail addresses), if you contact us. 

  * Your responses to surveys that we might ask you to complete for research purposes. 

  * Details of transactions you carry out through our Website and of the fulfillment of your orders. You may be required to provide financial information before placing an order through our Website. 

  * Your search queries on the Website. 

##  Information We Collect Through Automatic Data Collection Technologies. 

As you navigate through and interact with our Website, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns, including: 

  * Details of your visits to our Website, including traffic data, location data, logs and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Website. 

  * Information about your computer or mobile device and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system and browser type. 

The information we collect automatically is statistical data and we may maintain it or associate it with personal information we collect in other ways or receive from third parties. It helps us to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling us to: 

  * Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.

  * Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Website according to your individual interests. 

  * Speed up your searches.

  * Recognize you when you return to our Website. 

  * Recognize you when you return to our Website. 

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include: 

  * **Cookies (or browser cookies).** A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website. 

  * **Web Beaocns.** . Pages of our Website and our e-mails may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs. pixel tags and single-pixel gifs) that permit the Company, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or opened an e-mail and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity). 

We do not collect personal Information automatically, but we may tie this information to personal information about you that we collect from other sources or you provide to us. 

##  How We Use Your Information 

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information: 

  * To present our Website and its contents to you and other users. 

  * To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us. 

  * To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.

  * To provide you with notices about your account. 

  * To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us. 

  * To notify you about changes to our Website or any products or services we offer or provide though it. 

  * To allow you to participate in Interactive Services on our Website. 

  * To allow you to purchase license and download the Item. 

  * In any other way we may describe when you provide the information. 

  * For any other purpose with your consent. 

##  Disclosure of Your Information

We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction. 

We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy: 

  * To our subsidiaries and affiliates. 

  * To contractors, service providers and other third parties we use to support our business and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them. 

  * To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of Improve Presentation, Inc.'s assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by Improve Presentation, Inc. about our Website users is among the assets transferred. 

  * To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it. 

  * For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information. 

  * With your consent. 

We may also disclose your personal information: 

  * To comply with any court order, law or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request. 

  * To enforce or apply our terms of use Website Terms of Use, Privacy Policy, Copyright Policy, End User License Agreement and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes. 

  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of Improve Presentation, Inc., our customers or others. 

##  Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information 

We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information: 

  * **Tracking Technologies and Advertising.** You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function properly 

  * **Promotional Offers from the Company** If you do not wish to have your e-mail address or contact information used by the Company to promote our own or third parties' products or services, you can opt-out at any time by logging into the Website and adjusting your user preferences in your account profile by checking or unchecking the relevant boxes or by sending us an e-mail stating your request to [contact@www.improvepresentation.com](mailto:contact@www.improvepresentation.com) If we have sent you a promotional e-mail, you may send us a return e-mail asking to be omitted from future e-mail distributions. 

##  Accessing and Correcting Your Information 

You can review, change or delete your personal information by emailing us at [contact@www.improvepresentation.com](mailto:contact@www.improvepresentation.com)

##  Data Security 

We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration and disclosure. We encrypt information you provide to us using SSL technology 

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone. 

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. 

##  Changes to Our Privacy Policy 

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. 

##  Contact Information 

To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us at: [contact@www.improvepresentation.com](mailto:contact@www.improvepresentation.com)

US correspondence address:

Improve Presentation, Inc., 16192 Coastal Hwy, Lewes, Delaware 16192958, USA 

Please give 12-24 hours for our Support Team to get back to you on the problem. 

**Thank you for visiting www.improvepresentation.com!**
